<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="html_about">
        <![CDATA[
        <html>
		<head>
		</head>
		<body>
			Amazon App Notifier is a free and <a href="https://github.com/Skylark95/Amazon-App-Notifier">open source</a> notification manager for providing 
			notifications for the free app of the day on the <a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/mas/get-appstore/android">Amazon Appstore.</a><br/>
			<br/>
			Developer: Derek (Skylark95)<br/>
			Contact: derek@skylark95.com<br/>
			Website: <a href="http://www.skylark95.com/">http://www.skylark95.com/</a><br/>
			<br/>
			Thanks to the following open source projects:<br/>
			&#8226; <a href="http://actionbarsherlock.com/">ActionBarSherlock</a><br/>
			&#8226; <a href="http://commonsware.com/cwac">CommonsWare Android Components</a><br/>
			&#8226; <a href="http://wiki.fasterxml.com/JacksonHome">Jackson JSON Processor</a><br/>
			<br/>
			Others can be found in app description on play store and on GitHub project page.
		</body>
		</html>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="html_changelog">
        <![CDATA[
        <html>
		<head>
		</head>
		<body>
			Please send feature requests or bug reports to derek@skylark95.com or submit them on GitHub project page<br/>
			<br/>
			<b>Version 2.1.1-BETA - 5/6/2013</b><br/>
				Some Users reported the new notification icon was hard to see.  How about some different icon colors?  Find them in the settings menu.  Will add label to settings tab later.<br/>
				<br/>
			<b>Version 2.1-BETA - 5/4/2013</b><br/>
				Changed App icon at the request of Amazon.  If you can design a better icon email me ;)<br/>
				<br/>
				Changed App name at the request of Amazon.  Will move in you app drawer as name is now Free App Notifier<br/>
				<br/>
				Enabled in-app donations<br/>
				<br/>
				Added help button and help screen<br/>
				<br/>
				Added button to rate this app<br/>
				<br/>
			<b>Version 2.0.1-BETA - 4/18/2013</b><br/>
				If the device does not have an internet connection on boot, wait for a maximum of 5 minutes for a connection before timing out and displaying device offline notification<br/>
				<br/>
				Change notification text on offline notification to "No Internet Connection"<br/>
				<br/>
				Hopefully fixed force close bug that occurred on some Android 2.1 devices<br/>
				<br/>
			<b>Version 2.0-BETA - 4/8/2013</b><br/>
				Early beta release of newly rewritten app due to recent changes on Amazon breaking notifications for previous versions<br/>
				<br/>
				Completely rewritten with new UI and open source<br/>
				<br/>
				Expandable notifications for Android Jellybean<br/>
				<br/>
				Option to filter for apps with category "Games" (more category filters are planned)<br/>
				<br/>
				Currently known bugs:<br/>
				App developer section of notification sometimes shows private policy after the developer name<br/>
				<br/>
				Please email me (derek@skylark95.com) if you find any bugs or report them on the GitHub project page<br/>
				<br/>
			<b>Version 1.0.4 - 9/22/2012</b><br/>
				Small bug fix affecting free version<br/>
				<br/>
			<b>Version 1.0.3 - 9/21/2012</b><br/>
				If Appstore not found on phone, clicking notification redirects to download page<br/>
				<br/>
				Fix startup crash on some phones<br/>
				<br/>
			<b>Version 1.0.2 - 9/21/2012</b><br/>
				Added Option to disable vibrate<br/>
				<br/>
			<b>Version 1.0.1 - 08/13/2012</b><br/>	
				Fixed notifications not appearing on some phones (4.0 ICS, 4.1 Jelly Bean)<br/>
				<br/>
				Increased timeout for reading app name and price to 30 seconds (Less error downloading data messages on a slow connection)<br/>
				<br/>
				Fixed notification so when clicked on it launches the appstore on the main store page instead of the last open view (Get to downloading your free app faster!)<br/>
				<br/>
				 Works great on my new Nexus 7! :)<br/>
				<br/>
			<b>Version 1.0 - 05/16/2012</b><br/>
				Initial release
				<br/>
		</body>
		</html>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="html_uk_users">
        <![CDATA[
        <html>
		<head>
		</head>
		<body>
		    <p>Currently this app only gives notifications for what the free app of the day is in the US.</p>
		    <p>I have been working on adding an option to read what the UK free app of the day is. One problem I am facing right now though is 
		    where to pull the data for UK\'s free app of the day from.</p>
		    
		    <p>Right now the free app info for the US is pulled from this page...<br/>
		    <a href="http://www.amazon.com/mobile-apps/b?ie=UTF8&amp;node=2350149011">http://www.amazon.com/mobile-apps/b?ie=UTF8&amp;node=2350149011</a></p>
		    
		    <p>Problem is that amazon has not seem to have implemented the appstore into the UK domain <a href="http://www.amazon.co.uk/">amazon.co.uk</a>.
		    Until I can do a search for apps on the amazon UK domain, I don\'t yet have a solid way to pull info for the free 
		    app of the day in the UK.</p>
		    
		    <p>If you know somewhere where I can look up what the free app of the day is in the UK outside of the appstore app let me know by sending me 
		    an email at skylark95atc@gmail.com or submitting an enhancement at <a href="https://github.com/Skylark95/Amazon-App-Notifier/issues/">my page on GitHub</a> 
		    with the details.</p>
		    
		    <p>Many users have been requesting this feature and I would like to get it added</p>
		    
		    Thanks!<br/>
		    <b>Sky</b>
		</body>
		</html>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="html_help_text">
        <![CDATA[
		<b>Changing Settings</b>
		<p>Settings for this app can be access by pressing the <em>change settings</em> button on the settings tab as well as be accessed though the menu.</p>
		
		<p>The settings are organized in 2 sections: <em>Basic Settings</em> and <em>Advanced Settings</em>.  
		<em>Basic Settings</em> covers the essentials for the app, while <em>Advanced Settings</em> allows you 
		to fine tune more specific options.  Descriptions and current values for each setting can be found in the settings menu.</p>
		
		<b>Notification Update Time</b>
		<p>The Free App of the day on the Amazon App Store is updated around 12am PST (2am CST).  The data populated in the notification is 
		stored in a database on a shared server and is updated at this time.</p>
		
		<p>If Amazon pulls the Free app of the day and replaces it with another app, the notification may inaccurately 
		report what the free app of the day is (Although this doesn\'t happen too often).</p>
		
		<b>Testing the notification</b>
		<p>The notification can be tested with the settings you applied at any time by pressing the <em>test notification</em> button on the settings tab</p>
		
		<b>Installing Amazon Appstore</b>
		<p>If you do not have the Amazon Appstore installed on your device, pressing the <em>test notification</em> button on the settings tab 
		will give you a notification that prompts you to download the Amazon Appstore.  Pressing this notification will then take you to a page 
		where you can download the Appstore to your device.</p>
		
		<p>The download page will give instructions on how to install the app, but for reference, those instructions are:<p>
		<p>1. Open Settings and navigate to the Unknown sources option (under Applications or Security depending on your device).</p>
		<p>2. Tap the checkbox and then tap OK on the confirmation popup.</p>
		
		<p>Depending on your device, you may need to locate where files are downloaded to and select the downloaded APK file to install the Appstore</p>
		
		<b>Outside the US</b>
		<p>Currently this app only provides information that is accurate for the US version of the Amazon Appstore. This is 
		because I need to pull the information for the free app of the day from sources outside the Appstore and currently 
		this option is only avalible in the US.</p>
		
		<p>For more detail, press the <em>UK Users</em> button on the about tab</p> 
        ]]>
    </string>
    
</resources>